Guide to Papers of the Kellogg Family 1749-1945 MS 341
New-York Historical Society
- Box 23: Kellogg Family- Legal and Business Papers
  - Bills and Receipts: Remodeling the Port Kent House, 1892-1893 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1897-1898 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1907-1918 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Box 24: Kellogg Family- Bills and Receipts
  - Bills and Receipts, [1870-1920] (Box 24, Folder unknown container)
- Box 25: Kellogg Family- Bills and Receipts, and Grocer Account Books
  - Bills and Receipts, and Grocer Account Books, [1875-1905] (Box 24, Folder unknown container)
- Box 26: Kellogg Family- Books and Printed Matter
  - Maps (Loose), undated (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - A Certificate of "The Order of the Founders and Patriots of America", 1896 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - Invitation to the Opening Ceremonies of "the New York and Brooklyn Bridge", 1883 May 24 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Address of Welcome to the Charter Associates of the Order of the Founders and Patriots of America", 1896 Apr.17 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "A Natural History of the New-York Corn Exchange", 1875 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "The Chinese Theatre", undated (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "The Piano-forte Primer" (Julia Snow Kellogg's), undated (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Souvenir of Becket by Alfred, Lord Tennyson", 1893 Feb.6 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Souvenir of Shakespeare's King Henry the Eighth", 1892 Jan.5 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Souvenir of King Lear", 1892 Nov.10 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "New York & Brooklyn Bridge and Brooklyn City", 1883 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - Notebook: "Nutcracker and Sugardolly by F. Kellogg", undated (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Autobiography of Joseph Jefferson" (serialized in "The Century Magazine"), 1889 Nov.- 1890 Oct. (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "A True Copy of the Constitution of the United States", [1948] (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Bacon Versus Shakespeare; A Plea for the Defendant" by Thos. D. King (Presented to Gertrude Kellogg Nov.1877), 1875 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Grandmother Comstock's Singing Book", undated (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Historical Map of the War of the Rebellion April 1861 to April 1865", 1861 Apr.-1865 Apr. (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Book of Clippings" from Laura Comstock Dec. 25, 1921, 1921 Dec.25 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Guests" (Guest Book), 1899-1946 (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Frank Leslie's Popular Monthly", Vol.24, 1887 Aug. (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Autobiography of George Burwell Snow, D. D. S.", 1923 May (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  - "Album" (Newspaper Clippings), undated (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
- Box 27: Kellogg Family- Books
  - "The Holiday" by Joseph Allen D. D., Kellogg Library, [1847] (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "The Lu Lu Alphabet" (Fanny Kellogg Jan. 26, 1853), 1852 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Cousin Lucy At Study" by Jacob Abbott, Kellogg Library, 1849 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Any Thing for Sport" by Mrs. L C. Tuthill, Kellogg Library, 1847 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Lucy's Conversations" by Jacob Abbott, Kellogg Library, 1866 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Lucy Among the Mountains" by Jacob Abbott, Kellogg Library, 1854 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Lucy At Play" by Jacob Abbott, Kellogg Library, 1849 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Troublesome Tom" by Mrs. Sherwood, Kellogg Library, 1847 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Little Lessons for Little Learners" by Mrs. Barwell, 1854 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Frank and Fanny" by Clara Moreton, [1859] (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "The Play-Day Book: New Stories for Little Folks, by Fanny Fern", 1857 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Pictorial First Book for Little Boys and Girls" (Fanny Kellogg Nov. 17, 1855) (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Eleazer Williams, A Lecture" ( Read before the Chicago Historical Society Dec. 4, 1902), 1902 Dec. 4 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Leo Ross's Readings, No. 7, Mr. J. M. Bellew's Readings", 1879 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Edwin Booth's Prompt-Book of The Merchant of Venice, and Katharine and Petruchicio" (William Winter, ed.), 1881 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Out of an Horrible Pit, by T. J. Barnardo, F.R.C.S.E.", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "One Hundred Choice Selections for Readings and Recitations, No. 20", 1881 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Edwin Booth's Prompt-Book of Hamlet" (William Winter, ed.), [1878] (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Lacy's Acting Edition, Child of the Regiment", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Sensation Novels, Condensed.", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Camille", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "The Follies of a Night, by J. R. Planche", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "A Pretty Piece of Business, by Thomas Morton", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "The Two Bonnycastles, by John Maddison Morton", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Pure Gold, by Westland Marston, Esq.", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "Pygmalion and Galatea, by W. S. Gilbert", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "The Amateur Drama, Down by the Sea", undated (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  - "A Family Strike," by T. S. Denison, 1877 (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
- Boxes 28-31: Kellogg Family Photographs
  - Photographs, undated (Box 28, Folder unknown container)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 29, Folder unknown container)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 30, Folder unknown container)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 31, Folder unknown container)
  - Small Box of Photographs, undated (Box Unnumbered, Folder unknown container)
- Oversize Folder
  - Gertrude Kellogg, Sheet music, undated (Box Unknown container 483 for instance of Gertrude Kellogg, Sheet music, Folder unknown container)
  - Kellogg Family, Photographs, undated (Box Unknown container 484 for instance of Kellogg Family, Photographs, Folder unknown container)